// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Is this telling sentence or an asking sentence? \"I like dogs.\" ",
    answer: "Telling sentence",
    options: [
      "Telling sentence",
      "Asking sentence",
      "None of these",
      "Don't know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Is this telling sentence or an asking sentence? \"Where is your home?\" ",
    answer: "Asking sentence",
    options: [
      "Telling sentence",
      "Asking sentence",
      "None of these",
      "Don't know"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Pick the right question word \" __ can we go?\" ",
    answer: "when",
    options: [
        "what",
        "when",
        "None of these",
        "Don't know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Pick the right question word \" __ is the map?\" ",
    answer: "where",
    options: [
        "who",
        "when",
        "where",
        "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Find the complete sentence",
    answer: "we played",
    options: [
      "dog",
      "frog",
      "we played",
      "not"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Find the complete sentence",
    answer: "They asked me",
    options: [
      "six pups",
      "They asked me",
      "well",
      "not"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Fill in the blanks \"Ram __ football.\" ",
    answer: "plays",
    options: [
        "plays",
        "Raju",
        "eats",
        "None of these"
    ]
  }
  /*
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'r' ",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
      "V",
      "R",
      "W",
      "A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the letter 'C'",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
      "A",
      "Y",
      "C",
      "H"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Find the letter 'X'",
    answer: "X",
    options: [
      "V",
      "X",
      "A",
      "U"
    ]
  }
  */
];
